As a code in the cosmic feet Streaming ghosts through a silver bleed
I've been orbited Old versions of me
Deleting gravity Chasing a glitch in eternity
The sky's a mirror
slash where I go
That it can blow
We're wild like halos
Made of smoke
Every tear you fake
Drips mercury slow
Your mask is slipping through the cold
The hunger of the hollow
This ain't this wild old sorrow
You won't
service, show me me heaven and hell we're binary lies when I ascend your ego dies
Go no flesh or vice
Go
Watching me heaven and hell with both my screens when I'm light the dark reading
I'm sorry. Hold on.
You see me yet? Okay.
I'm going to hop in the bath though.
I mean, what can I do between then?
I mean, what do you think is going to come up with?
I'm sure you're going to all want to come up when I get back.
Very clean. Okay.
I can play about Alexandra taking the boxing championship.
Okay, let's see what we got.
Hold on a second.
OK.
OK, watch this while I'm gone.
Hi, guys.
Just watch this while I'm gone.
It's fun.
You don't even exist, do you?
You thought of nothing, do you?
We have more, we represent, Vita, we represent,
fucks, fucks, fucks, fucks, fucks, fucks, fucks, fucks.
I don't know what else to call it,
but what else to call it, hold on, hold on,
we need your psyche to listen to.
I have no idea, she's literally fucking obsessed
and keeps doxing my name and last name, thinking it's funny,
fun, like one, like, one, like, node, she says,
Carl is like crazy on the other node,
where she says he's not, like,
I don't know why she didn't even ring and crawl in so that she can just like go on like date him or whatever she's a little obsessed with crawl too I guess I don't know she said that I would like me and you have like a some kind of ring going on you know like that
We're all going to go ahead and draw.
But she's like bringing up KK and she's like, oh look, look at how he's talking to KK.
He'd be like the kind that would like do this and that and then on the other end, she's like saying, he's perfect for me.
Like, what the fuck do you want from me, lady?
And I was talking to a car right there.
I mean, she missed on, she missed on the film.
I was talking to a car when I said something like that.
Yeah, she backwards said to her benefit.
Like, she'll just back forward things and she's like, look right here.
Look.
And not only that and that's why I got a lot of time to play it quick. She changed your full name a lot of times
That's something very cautious with that. You know people, you know, I can't spell your name
You know, shut up to me shut up to your name. Yeah, I can't spell that
You gotta be careful, you know, she do that and whatever
Yeah, she is doctrine. She don't go fuck. I don't go you know, you don't deserve none of that
She got she got close to sight because of you that you want to be close to car
If you could be you now I'm thinking about it. Maybe you can't be close to me that was close to you, too
He's the game. I think it's all your fault. No, I'm just kidding
I think she it really has it out for you or anyone that's like associates with you
Then she thinks they're part of whatever but at the same time
She just needs like someone to um, she's a bully, you know, she's like an internet bully
She likes to like make fun and laugh like the witch
She thinks she's like so like amazing, but then on the other end she'll go and do these like Bible readings
Like she's like insane and it's like you have really bad energy
You're a sight to belong together. You guys are both fucking weird
Yeah
Alex was crazy when I saw her on my own panel
She's nuts. I thought and she lies and she's all I do have to do to defend myself
She reached out to me and I took my time to talk to her.
Because she was going through something.
I didn't call my father either.
I know Alex.
I didn't share nothing actually with Alex.
I was just giving him my ear when she was going through something.
I'm like that.
All right.
Now me, Defender Alex wins.
I don't need to be Defender Alex.
I always said, he will fear her.
Y'all need to stop turning him into fear.
He's the original person.
So that's what she does.
I got Ben saying Alex's taking people to the weirdo.
He does, he takes shit too far.
He's like the other country.
You can even make stories up in his head.
Now, I see Psycho on the panel,
Dita, he's just taking stories in his fucking head.
I ain't really trying to cook a little cooking
on his head, but he really loves it.
I don't have to try to fix your name.
I'm gonna, to see him on the panel, go ahead.
Look, he gets like fucking mad because some people like, oh, I'm concerned about the chapter or whatever.
This and that. JDogg was on his panel and he was saying nasty shit about, you know, like you or, you know, what happened with your dog.
And he was just sitting there quietly saying nothing. He doesn't intervene and be like, JDogg, that's fucked up.
Don't talk about that shit. That's sensitive. Listen to that. He just sits there and like smiles and like consumes it.
And then he cries that, oh my God, a lot of people don't like me. They judge me. They, you know, but then do fucking.
better and like Christine like she was on the panel um someone has told them like several times
you know what you're playing with like Crystal and it is like a fucking subject and you start
playing it oh yeah yeah just playing and he jumped off and he started the life like playing that
While he was do that
Everybody that supported him Christine you even he attacked pain. Why the fuck you're taking pain
And then you say, yeah, and then I think they can follow.
He's got Alex and the two Mexicans, no disrespect to my Mexicans.
You're a company and and they go to lazy ass Mexicans.
I'm never seeing lazy Mexicans in my life.
Listen, I'm not crying over the fucking guy. I was like, I was doing my own panel last night
I have like, you know, it was like for Katie's birthday and he said, you know, Mason over there and
You know, Mason was like, I don't know why he sent me over here
And I was like, I don't know either and then all of a sudden a couple of people send me screenshots
They're like, he's restraining you, you know, like an art interaction with me
So now they try to explain to me son, you know, that's not the best place like, you know
Nothing against you. You are nice. I see you. You'd be nice. Yeah. So then he goes and then he comes back on my panel last time
We're playing trivia little more cordially was nice to him. Even though I was kind of like
Fucking tired and you being fake or whatever then he goes today and starts doing his bullshit again
And I told him, I was like, you're, you know, you do this and then you're like, get upset.
Like how many chances do I have to get?
And someone came up on his panel and she was like, if you know, that's like really bothers
like somebody that was a supporter of yours.
Like Christine, just don't play that fucking clip over and over again.
Well, yeah, yeah, fine, fine.
And then he'll do it.
He doesn't give, he had no respect, no respect.
Okay, he runs behind people. I noticed that he don't want to talk. They don't want to talk about like I don't really care
Why do you keep going with the same old shit same old shit same old shit?
Yeah, neither on my summer like literally I let him on my panel last night everything was cool
And then he goes back and he just starts again with like, you know, this AI song in the bullshit and like
oh you know a bunch of people in your chat don't like me and I'm like you know you're like J-Dog
and like most of the people that hate me modded in fact he went as far as to mod Carl which I don't
have anything against like Carl being a mod but I know that he was being vindictive and he was
I'm sorry for you. You did it with Carl. They've got to deal with sight and I did not deal with a other weirdo like
I can't catch a break and before that I was dealing with raging demon before that I was dealing with cake the turtle
It's just like I can't catch a fucking break, you know
Then be sexy that you create this green and create the problem. What do you say?
I feel for there and like you know entertain me being talk shit about
You know get ready we have more you are be the we have more you are
You got they're gonna get a psycho panel
All right
Mushrooms I took mushrooms. All right, so you're gonna open your mouth. What's that?
No, no, I'm sorry. Tell me I'm sorry. Tell me I'm in backup
If people want to fight it, I'll be right there to fight it like you.
And it's me who's not that motherfucker, so sit in that damn corner, J-Doc, cause you ain't shit to an old judge.
They know what you're talking about.
Fuck you, bitch.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I'm just saying about you that you try to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it's about the world, like how am I going to act like it
You're going to taxing a bunch of fucking women from class 6.
What about I'm only the equal rights?
You guys want equal rights?
Stop!
Three, two, one, get out of here.
Get, get, get, get, get, get, get, get out of here.
Let him out of here standing.
Good luck with whoever did that.
Thank you.
Go live.
I don't know what it is.
Right, who gets the other cookie?
You go live, you want to compete.
And you want to play your x-ray?
One of his posts here about people on her panel,
and then you want to see who's moving in there.
But my dog, you can talk about it a little bit.
Right?
You call me nothing but a little bit on your panel.
Yes or no?
Yeah, you can bring it up and I will
let you know if you appreciate it.
Thank you.
Well, you don't need to bring up nothing, right?
Can I ask you why you broke Christine's name
in the title today?
He says Christine was yelling on his channel and I was telling her a good thing that I think it would be so wrong with this stuff that I was like, okay Christine, there's another clip of you talking in a good way.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Don't take a crop of him. Please get out of here.
Yeah, but then he does this fucking too. And you know, he cries like Michael many, many times and then later on he's like, oh I never did like so long.
Come on. Jesus. I mean that's the thing is like he goes over and over, over and over,
like Christine told him this is rubbing me the wrong way. I keep telling him it's not
fucking fun and like jokes and games when you're going low like that. But then he's like,
Well, you know, I just don't understand why we should continue to do this. It's real
simple. Like, we don't have much trouble. There's a lot of people that we're just
trying to support if you like me. And they're a perp. And you're not seeing
this as a perp.
I was going to tell them, you don't want people to talk about a fucking little box.
A little box.
He didn't show me my pictures.
I was literally telling him, you're hurting me when you're talking about my ex that healed
a real good man and you're like literally saying all this stuff, should I just be like,
oh, it's just comedy, it's just fun, doesn't that?
It's like, no, I'm telling you how I feel.
People are telling you like they're hurt and now you got, you know, gay dogs and whoever
else in your fucking ear.
And it's like, dude, some ships like, is it friendship?
Because if it's not friendship, then it's just fair game and everybody's open fucking
I guess everybody's fucking up and see if that's what we do, but I thought we were all friends and those
won't continue just to go back and forth and hurt each other. I just don't get a summer. He makes
something be cool with beer and all that and then he lets these people get in his ears.
I don't know what the fuck is going on with Alex. He's off the fucking spectrum even more and more.
That's just loud. It's loud as fuck, man.
He's doing the pre-image fucked up.
The way you mentioned Paige, what the fuck do you mean?
You're mad about Paige, man.
You go, how? Why are you mad about Paige?
That Paige is in there.
Paige wanna hang with beautiful little dude
and forget about going to your camera,
look to your chat.
Let Paige do her. She'll come back to you.
It's you two they come back
That's your home girl. They come back. He likes to push buttons and it's like a pretty
Evil the way he is because you're directly telling him. This is bothering me, but he's just like I'm gonna do it more
Just to piss you off. It's so weird, you know
It's like
And Jago is a fucking clown's room.
He's a fucking weirdo-ass nigga.
I mean, I didn't have a shit.
I'm fucking trying to give him a punch.
Like, all of a sudden, he's just,
like I said, Jago, I want to jump up here.
Don't lie, don't lie.
Ain't nobody talking to you, you fucking,
you're gonna find your fucking wife's lame ass motherfucker.
Yeah, and Jago was over there to support me and stuff,
but he was like, oh my God, you can't do this.
And he came on his own.
But you know what?
You had like four people walking in,
like fucking you and yourself here.
So five of you didn't want to do it, is that fair?
Nothing fancy.
Then you're saying, I can't find my own dial,
and you have to put the blue inside.
And then you just put the false screw in it.
Oh!
Well, it still can be, but it's like,
let's move that to draw, let's move it.
OK.
Did you see it or it was it off?
Hey, dear dog. Oh, that's a nice shower
Take my rings
You see him
Look at that beautiful gold
Anyway
You know the cult leader shirt, so yeah
Yeah
Okay, oh shoot it probably put my hair back. Hey, Lenore want to come up and say hi. This is my this is Lenore the
You happy? She's a happy cat
Today what's his name?
Sean see Sean James Tommy James
Was like
I was like, I'm holding the cat like either by her arms or like and just like lightly touching under her
She's very comfortable. She would be like, no, don't, you know, she's very comfortable. Okay. Obviously anyone knows anything about cats
They're not gonna frickin
Let you, you know, man handle them unless it's, you know, you're giving good rubs, right?
Okay
Okay. Let me grab my, uh, something. Let me see.
Oh my, rubber bands. Look what I have, guys.
It's called a boob bucket. A boob bucket.
You're gonna, you're never too, you're never too old for a bucket.
Luckily for me this also doubles as a hat
Kind of like a nutcracker kind of kind of vibe got some ketchup
Look it's disappeared. It looks like I'm just wearing a halo, right, but it's actually McDonald's move bucket
Like it
They have a black cat one. I really want but yeah, it is have these
Loose a zombie pumpkin base woman or something. I know what if I look like this guy's like you like still like me
I look like that
Disappearing I look like that. Hi guys. What if I look like that? What'd you do?
You just leave my show forever not talk to me anymore. I had a mohawk though. It's pretty cool mohawk. Yeah, man
It is a mohawk look
Clever oh
My god
J-Dog
What are you doing?
Okay, anyway, let's see. I have stickers now. I'm gonna put some stickers down. What do I have stickers? I have a spiderweb
Here you go put that on my
Okay, you put it right there my word. Oh, we have seen that is
I'm gonna put them all over my keyboard over here. So they're glow-in-the-dark supposedly that we should be pretty cool. Oh shit, okay
Hello necessary. Hi
Geez, I mean do you think theme theme at the school of Athens?
Does he have like some kind of I don't know. It's like he doesn't get up. It's a point
He just makes it in there and not only that he's heart. He's criticizing me on my own show like oh like why do you care?
Hello, it's like I just
Tell someone to like, you know, hush
He what I don't know exactly what you're talking about. There was a lot of confusion going on there people talking all at once
I was confused about the whole the whole thing where he's like, oh, you know, it's like, you know
Why why are you donating it? I don't know. It's like he's like, oh, I'm not asking why are you donating?
I'm just asking why are you donating it? It's like, okay, well
Oh, but the donation thing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah that whole are yeah, I don't think it's like it's like none of his business or
Really, it's a really anybody's business. It's like, you know, why is it all of a sudden? It's like, it's not that you don't know
Psych I don't think the donations
and it being known.
I know, it's like he runs a band, but you know what?
There might be stuff going on behind the scenes
that you don't know, like people don't know about,
and we might have certain,
have come to understandings and arrangements,
and it's like...
Oh, okay, fine.
It's just, I think people will take issue with the way
that Ghost seems to flaunt it,
and lord it over people.
A lot of donators in this community...
Yeah, I'm just saying I think that's the issue. I don't think the issue is you getting donations. Honestly, I don't think that
Because it's like why isn't anybody else say oh well this person donated this for this and that it's like no it's all about
Oh my god goes it's like don't do that like it's like anyways. No, I don't know. I think you misunderstand
I I don't think it's the actual donations. I think it's the way that
Goes I will think of personally when you're talking about my stuff like my my donations and my show and all that kind of
How I run my show it's like if I was to just like like ghosts, you know on my streamer panel and run the shit
I could do that if I wanted to
Could I could I definitely
I'm not yelling at you. I'm just saying it's like I can run my show how I feel like running my okay
I don't even care about that. Listen man. This beat of shit has got to stop. Okay. Why do you keep?
I could I could find what what happened
Don't play innocent man. This beat of shit has to stop. Okay. You got to leave her alone
mentioning her stop mentioning her stop
Doesn't talk about you she talks about you only when she gets asked and she only gets asked about you because you do something
So stop doing shit
Rita will not be talking about me in other ways. Okay, please
Kathy
This isn't good for you, man. It's not good for you
You're the one freaking out thing that is I'm fine, right? Okay
But yeah, if I don't care, why should anybody right? It's RG. I believe you yeah
But anyway thing that is it's like why do you why are you so up on it?
Like I like why are you so interested like I don't know
It's like you're like getting a little bit like in the middle of words like not really your business
I've known Bita longer than you.
I've had a relationship longer than you.
I know how we talk to each other.
I know our relationship.
It's like all these people getting in the middle saying,
oh, do you leave her alone?
You leave her?
It's like, I am leaving her alone.
Okay, you don't need to.
You're not leaving her alone, though.
You're not?
No, you're not.
I'm not.
Okay.
Well, that's your opinion.
It's like, if I play her on my show,
she would be like, that was, I was in that clip.
I was clipped.
It's like part of the panel verse lore now, right?
And people don't know what's going on.
They can see.
It's a little bit of a reminder.
in case people, so people don't have to say,
what happened with you and Bita?
My concern here is that I like you both
and I like going on both of your panels
and it puts me in a tough position.
You knew that she wants you on the panel.
No, no, no, no.
Me and Bita do not talk behind the scenes.
Everything that you've seen, every video
or anything you've seen of me and Bita talking
are the only times we've spoken.
We do not talk behind the scenes at all.
I haven't either in a long time.
So it's like everything that you've seen
Right on okay. I just want to get that clear. There's not like there's a conspiracy. I'm not planning with anybody
You know, there's I know you're not in the conspiracy as far as I know, but mr. Canadian, you know
expert, but okay, okay, it's just I do the same with Peter that I do with you
I don't talk to you behind the scenes either, okay
That's we are adults. We are adults. I know you're like a little bit older than us
But it's like, you know, not that much older than us and so it's like, you know
Viewers to understand
Like me being here like where I stand. I think I have no no communications with either of you behind the scenes
This is all
On video and all streams and what you guys are doing. Okay. Now. I know with beta
beta I wasn't
dragging
I need to have a 15 minute clip. I saw a trip kick where I saw I was on Jerry Springer
And I thought it was the longer one, but I didn't
But you don't see how this is a cycle
You keep saying, oh, I see something somewhere.
Someone said something about me with Mida and all that stuff.
So you play it, and then somebody asked Bita, but,
and Bita's like, oh, I wish he'd just leave me alone.
Just stop mentioning me or whatever, OK?
And then it comes back around.
And then this becomes worse again.
You don't even know.
I mean, jeez, everybody thinks, oh, we
know exactly what's going on in the relationship.
But yeah, we see everything that's going on.
Seriously, it goes deeper than that. Okay, but anyway
Like I don't want to say harassing but it is
It is pestering man. It's it's get harassing her. He's the one that actually clipped her show is he her is trippi cake messaging her
Did I?
Yes, but we were on talking terms when I messaged her. We okay even though the last message before that said
Maybe said don't contact me again
We were still talking between that and so we were and then when I did that first message
She used to had a good reception and the second message which was actually a nice message
She has an evil reception. And so it's like, okay, she's just doing the opposite of what I do. It's like, yeah
year-olds
She asked you to leave her alone, right? And she put it pretty well in that message that we went over the okay
Go away. I mean, you're just annoying. I mean, it's like what oh leave her alone
I'm leaving her alone. What could I play some stupid clip? I mean, she's part of the part of the show
Okay, I did a clap. I'd like you know or whatever the
Dish I made some shorts and whatever and she's not in the latest shorts. It's all auto and flirty diamond
Okay, I had to go to the bathroom. I saw a clip of my face on it. Okay, so I played it
Okay, is that a big deal? I just knew it was some bullshit. Probably, you know, about that idea. I was in the bath. Okay
You're harping on me again. It's like you're harping on me. I don't feel like being harped on. Okay. I'm an adult
Don't tell me if you know is oh, so what this is restraining order restraining order territory now that
You know, I've played a clip of her and that I was in on my show and she's talking about me in the clip
I mean, it's like I'm not allowed to do that. Hello
You're bringing her up right now. You're causing me to talk about her right now. I wouldn't be talking about her right now
I was ready to come back here and talk about anything else
You're harping on me. I don't like it
I don't like this playing dumb shit man. It's fucking
It's it's an insult to me, man. Okay. Well, you're insulting me again. Bye. Okay. Hi, Yumi. How are you?
Oh you me
Okay, well, you know, obviously I just want to be people just want to bitch at me for no reason. It's okay. So I
Know well
You know, I will say Alexander Meyers taught me a little bit about sticking out for myself, okay
Just like cut the bullshit, okay, I like how she is cut the bullshit cut the shit, okay?
I'm not playing dumb. I said what I did, right? What am I doing beyond what am I doing? That's so bad. Hello
Hello, am I doing something bad not listening to her show. She's going on all these different shows
We're referring but not saying my name. Okay, but she's not talking about me. No, no, she's not
Right. Oh gosh because people are expecting her to write it's like as soon as they don't she's gonna start fucking doing it again
Okay, as soon as you start expecting me to I'm gonna stop. Okay, so get your expectations in line people
Maybe it's like you guys
You me I didn't say it you're here. Hello. Yeah
I'm in the show. Oh, hi
Hi, how are you? Oh
Good, how are you? I'm not bad
Yeah, I'm just voicing my opinion and also. Yeah, if you don't want to be talked about don't have a show
Okay, don't have a show
Don't have a show a call-in show where everyone can call in, right?
Don't do that. Just go into hiding go into obscurity go into witness protection program
Change your phone number, you know, you know all this kind of stuff, right?
What I won't end well what?
It was already not gonna end well what it's gonna end worse than it was
When I just dropped the drama I did who just brought it up thing that is I was on to other stuff
What happened?
I just played it like a clip when I took a bath real quick. I even know what clip it was
I didn't even hear it from the bathroom. I came back turned it off and
Oh my god, bronze birds in here. Who cares?
Whoa, Bronzeberg. Oh, you tried bronze. Oh my gosh. This is a crisis now. Oh my gosh, please. I dare you. I dare you say
I'm doing anything wrong. I dare you. What am I doing?
So, he's still working at you?
Isn't it ironic? I mean, this is one of the biggest gang stalkers in California, right? Her, right?
And it's like all of a sudden, I'm the stalker, right?
Oh, okay, I tried bronze. Well, you're sitting there talking to bronze, trying to plot and tell me things, okay?
Good thing maybe you're not on my panel. You Sorcerer, Warlock, whatever you are, Canadian Mind Control, MKLtra, trainer.
How are you?
I know all about you.
Okay.
Oh, Sherry. Okay, Sherry's berries.
Go bury your face in some shit. I don't care. Go away. Yeah, I'm not bothered
Just leave me alone leave me
People so if you guys do not like from the side chat go away
Yeah, I mean, it's like what I know ghost likes to argue and stuff. Okay, argue with go
You don't think they're argue with ghosts you argue with me all the time. I want to argue with me
Do you see them the rules that says don't argue with me?
Done with it. I
Be nice and have a show for you guys. I
Didn't I didn't come here like
Like, I mean, not awesome because since I mean, yeah, this, this people, this people try to, you know, it's better, it's better. It's better. I, I, it's the way that I respect the society only.
Yeah
Everyone's like, oh, you know women are you know like the beginning if I said if I was when I first met beat if I was and she was on the
Panel if I was to say don't call beat a bitch. She would say
Don't defend me. I could stick up for myself. Yeah, okay
That's what she did right and pie to the same thing then when I don't offend her
You need to defend me. Okay. Okay. I mean jeez and it's like and then it's like behind the scenes
Do you know like she does have a flying monkey army?
I mean, it's like, yeah, someone, someone said it, someone said it to me about playing
one key song.
Thank you.
She predict them in her chat.
No, they get attacked and they get upset and they come tell me about it.
So whatever.
Okay.
there's more going on than you think please thanks thanks thanks to you the psyche finally you
can realize what flying monkey is oh i know i've known a new me i'm an expert in narcissistic
abuse because i've you know i've uh you're safe now you'll be okay this is like well i mean
to hate someone, to attack someone, you know, that's not.
Oh my gosh, it's like I was probably put in that situation.
Oh, come defend, come defend, come defend.
And it's like all of a sudden, I don't even know what I'm defending
or the story necessarily, right?
And it's like all of a sudden, like, I'm getting involved all of a sudden
and things I don't want to be involved in here.
Look at that. I fixed it. There we go.
Wow. Hey, you know, can I see something?
Yes.
You look so fresh today.
I like what you really look fresh today. You're fresh. Thank you. I just take a shower. I have my beer
I think that is is not like draining me mentally with his powers tonight. So I'm feeling a little bit better
That's good. That's really good
Oh, yeah. Oh, Yumi, how have you been? Did you see my friend, uh, Chona the other night? She came on the show.
How have I been? I've been, I was busy with my teaching class. You're busy? Oh no. Yeah.
And I, I was, I was on someone's panel yesterday while I'm teaching. Yeah.
Did you, did you, did you celebrate the Halloween this is like?
And I didn't dox beta because beta everything that I said beta said herself on I have it on tape. She says that herself on the air with me and
And you can go to the post and the post is not doxing
Even the society is gay. He's still a man
Is bronze is bronze chicken screaming in the chat or something
He's still crying. Yes. What is he saying?
What's he saying? Yeah, this morning. He's still talking about us about you and he's talking about me. I don't know
Well, you know, be the myself in Janet world docs at the same time
beta is on great terms with the person that Docs does in fact, I think he
You know, he's a friend of her show
Look how, look how the way, look how the way this like monkey slendery view about Miss Peta.
Yeah.
That's really sad.
She said herself is not on me to repeat.
Well, okay, so if like Julia Roberts says her name is something on the air in front of like everybody on her show, on her own show.
And then it's like, I have a clip of it.
Saying her whole everything right is that doxing? No, that's information is already out there plus. She is a
Thanks, God, I'm not a bad person I never trolling people I never doxing people
I never make fun with people pictures. I never make fun with people's faces. I mean
I don't know.
She called Ron's a flying monkey.
Oh, is that a smashed Hebrew hammer?
Is that the same person?
I don't like that person.
Yeah, she called Ron's a flying monkey, OK?
Flying monkey.
It's a narcissism term about the person
that goes attacks on behalf of the person.
Yes, Ron's bird is the flying monkey.
OK, there we go.
And I got a geo.
You don't understand if you look up flying monkey.
It's a narcissist.
It's not anything racial, OK, guys?
Not like you guys you guys who became a flying monkeys you guys are part of narcissistic person
Yeah, exactly narcissistic personality is really really dangerous
They can manipulate him. They can doxing you. They can play their games. They can
They can lie to you, they can pretend at you, so I stay away from them all.
They can make it seem like everything's your fault, they can turn everyone against you,
they're very charming, they're very manipulative, they do things that normal people wouldn't do,
so they can't, you know, it's like, they'll go dirtier, and it's like if you wrestle with pigs,
you know, you get dirty, the pig likes it, so it's like, you know, it's not even worth it.
I've been attacked, I've been attacked a while ago on someone's channel, some of flying monkeys, some of flying monkeys, this narcissistic personality told me he has a man, told me he has a dick, told me I look like a man, told me my name.
He looked like a man.
Yeah, yeah
That's ridiculous, I mean that's ridiculous I've been on I've been on
Camera several times. I've shown my proof. I
Showed my everything about me. I feel my even my job and thanks God no trust cannot
Docs me
Because I protect my students, I protect my university, the place that I work, I protect my family, I protect my private life.
So for trolls, cyber trolls, come up here and show yourself. Do not judge in us, do not judge in me, do not judge in the society.
Because me and the society is a real one, real real human, real real face.
Yeah, Bronzeberg can just cry into the ether. I don't even see him. It's like and it's so nice because it's like he's so bitchy
I mean, it's like Bronzeberg talk about like bitching. I mean come on
He attacked me a while ago
Wow
He thinks he thinks he has he thinks he has he has everything I mean he never showed himself in the public
Right. I heard he's like not even like like really black. He's one K subscribers
But going on panel, that's a good, that's a good, that's not the real streamer, the real streamer, it looks like, it looks like him, looks like he's a psyche, show, show him style, you know, and making like a content.
make a song, that's the real streamer, not you,
Brunsburg, you hiding, you're the hide and face,
you're the hidden face, that's me, you're not a streamer,
you're not, thanks God, I'm not a part of you, Brunsburg.
That was out of bounds, fuck off, Smash, come on.
What did I say that's out of bounds?
Okay, let's let's change the topic. This is actually okay. I want to talk I want to talk about I want to do like a little like
cleansing
Ritual okay, you like the ritual
Ritual
Ritual.
It's Ritual.
It's Saturday.
It's Saturday. It's Saturn.
Okay, so Saturn.
Okay, so what time is it?
Let me see.
It is 11.
Oh, it's only 10, 10.
Okay, so we have a couple.
Okay, so I'm going to do, I'm going to burn moon incense.
I'm going to burn
Pluto incense and I'm going to burn
And then I'm going to put some Jupiter in there just to like balance out the it is because it's kind of
Some uh
Some little bit of more more extreme energies in there. So I'll bounce that with some Jupiter. So it'll be just it'll be like a softening of
I'll tell you what I'll do
And I have really nice I really good cleansing
So I have these charcoal you light and I have some incense
Cleansing cleansing fine monkeys from the side
Drugging monkeys. I like that song
Someone someone sending someone sent to me the flying monkey song by society. It's really cool
Really really cool
Thank you
Oh, how are you? How about your cats? How are they fine? They're great
They are you know, I had been my cat pie came back
mm-hmm
For a little day and then he then he left but he just and he just came and rubbed against my leg and then
And
My other cats are good my friend bro over her cat get a day. It was like a little black and white cat named Figuero
and
Yep, I'm just very lucky
Flying monkeys on this court the NPD on this court
Well, yeah, everybody can like, you know, like you can research what flying monkeys are and like, you know
Well, you know, unfortunately a lot of people don't realize till it's too late and these are very
You
They they try to backstab you try to
Controlling your panel your channel, you know, just be careful like a like a bomb. I don't I don't I don't get it
Why some people really like oh
There's that people, you know, they're just sad people
Yeah, I mean, they're like so jelly
A streamer like you have a lot of friends have a lot of subscribers have a lot of viewers
You know, I mean, I don't even have a lot of I mean, it's like I have like, you know a great great people a great quality of people
But I have a various like today. I had like five people in the chat like a lot of people like don't like
Care for music. They don't care for
just me doing different things like you know me reading or me doing astrology it's like
just want the fuck shit and i say i i made an effort not to like bring up
fuck shit all day i did play that i will always remember that you gave me like a seven teacups
The eight three cups. Yeah, I really like it. That's that's me. That's really me
I mean, I don't like I don't like pretenders. I don't like they owe you me. I like you but in the back
He or she talks shit about me. I don't like it. I really know how to deal with this kind of person
It's called just no contact. You just like and I regret like, you know playing that clip just now
If it was such as like a incendiary thing, you know, I don't want to
Keep ringing her up. But yeah, I do have to address some things because it's like
I'm now I'm being labeled as
Do you have any new song today? I do would like to hear a song
Can you
You you really I I saw every video a I someone by
Love this
He shall spell
Alexander's preaching with a tan
So divine sunscreen
Forgotten he's turning to brine
With a lobster, people red and raw
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law
that is whispers the pot can't wait Alexanderizes halo of foam welcome
microstations to your new home with the lobster people red and raw
snapping our claws at the cosmic law
Opps to people, red and raw
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law
Steaming our veins, salting our...
It was so fun.
It was fun.
I like that.
Everybody got something.
That's fun.
Yeah.
I like that wet trap.
You like the wet trap?
From the Christmas land?
Yeah.
Red side beach.
Shit.
Well done. This is like well done. Well done. Thanks. Do what you want to do. Do what you want to do.
Do what you want to do. Do what you want to do. Do what you want to do.
For the folks who tried to bring you down.
Do not let them bring you down this is like.
Lay me down.
Yeah.
Trolls. Hello trolls. Hello haters. Hello.
Hey, we're doing the duet hey, they say that love and we get old
Well, we know it's hilly
We grow bulls. Oh, it's Jimmy. I don't know mr. Stike. You don't stand with the flying monkey
Why is any of me miss miss Jamie is then for the circus fans forever
She's a cowgirl. She she she lassos flying monkeys
Yeah, yeah, she's she's stand for that. I I don't get it. Okay, they never came
You know what if we're just have to agree to disagree
I mean, it's like there's my five friends don't always get along with everybody else. I I know a lot of
Anyway, yeah
I've never heard of the person what's what's he like?
Oh, yes. Oh, yes. I know him. Yeah, he told me as a man today. He called you a man.
But do you know that Joe has born with the vagina? He's very insecure about it. He has
Will be a troll
Trolls got a troll
They that way you put a green on your face you're by putting your goblin under a bridge
You're like Cyrax is that what you do it or are you doing blackface to make them a black? Oh, it's you mean my face
Blackface for hours
or the green. Oh, wait, I'll show you. Are you wearing it now? Oh, no, I'm in trouble. It's
MRFs. Oh, there it is. Oh, my gosh.
Look you have in our pictures of it. It's not for facial. This is if you if you wear that
My face look looks a little bit a little bit
Have you ever thought about wearing it clean? Yeah a little bit clean. I mean wait
I'm thinking about just start just wearing a mask and then like I'm not worried about my skin anymore. Oh, you look beautiful. You look beautiful. Oh
Yeah
Hey, is that made of the four skins of Korean babies?
This is this is what I wear
This skin, this is the top ingredient. Does it say four skins?
I don't know
I, this is, I, I, I, um, one of my friends gave me advice, I mean, they gave me to use this for, for cleaning my face from the dust from the, you know.
They said you need to, they say you need to wash off that, um, that mud mask.
Yep, yep, yep.
Deep forest
Cleaning play max. Oh, okay. That makes sense. Yeah, exactly
I don't know. I don't know what some I don't know what many people from from side chat thought that I
Try to be a vastness
Learn this a little bit. I think it was when you when you brought up when you had the hat and the cane on and then you were talking
That weird voice
I mean this is not even this is not even this is not even black I mean this is blue color
it's a great great great I know it's literally blue in your color yeah it's literally your color
yeah it's a blue it's a blue it's not a dark it's not a dark I think like this maybe only the people
that would be offended are small and they don't really exist yeah or is this one guy that but
Yes. Look, how to, oh, wait, it's really,
we are using my phone, look.
What are you, oh my god, is it gray?
Is it gray?
What is that?
It's almost empty.
Oh, it's empty.
Oh, throw that away.
Well, it's a mask that I put on my face every Sunday.
That's your mask?
It's like it's like it's completely clean like it's like it's frosting. Yeah like that like that like like
like that. That'd be a funny prank. It's only it's only it's only look it's only for woman
I think it's about you, yeah, a special woman who likes to, you know, to have a good time.
Alhamdulillah, thanks God, Alhamdulillah.
Alhamdulillah?
I had a good time.
Alhamdulillah means thanks God.
Oh, Alhamdulillah.
Yeah, Alhamdulillah.
Like that?
Alhamdulillah!
Thank you for the sighting. Yeah, Alhamdulillah.
Are you good?
Yeah, very good. Are you good to me?
Are you good to me?
That's the only other word I know.
Actually, I'm just kidding.
Okay, 24-7?
I don't know.
Tired to be like another 23 hours tonight
I heard you used to be in the ff and we want you I want to
You come back. We're not monkeys. I mean you keep calling us monkeys
I mean, they know I've now I've been I've been absorbed into the cold. They've been absorbed into my
Psychi is a king of cats. Yeah
Yeah
The king of cats is a cat lover
Yes, I really I really my husband my husband
Love cats his black cat name
What is it?
Pantora Pantora Pantora, yeah
Pantora. Pantora. Pantara. Pantora. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara. Pantara
Everything about cats you me. Can you say pronounce after me poot day poot day? It's really fun to say
Yeah, what is it?
Pute like a like a hairy black put a yeah put a like it means you like cats
Yeah
Um, you mean have you seen this clip right here?
He's a little smarter than he's letting on bro because when he went over to beat us and I did see that
He went over there and he straight up lied on you psyche like straight up me and Jamie. I saw him
He said psyche sent me over here psyche sent me over here. Why did psyche send me over here when you'd never dig send him over there?
You just read them you recommended it. Hey, if you want to see
He's like, what's that woman's name?
And I said her name is Vita or Sarah.
Yeah, you just corrected it.
That's all you did.
You didn't tell him, hey, go harass her or go over there and say,
hey, psyche send me over.
You never said any of that.
You know, I wouldn't do that.
I don't not.
They have a person that would even send people over to troll.
The only way to send the people over is to be nice and to help
help their chat or whatever.
you know I'm just gonna be but also I do believe Mason is autistic um and talking to uh Queen
Natalie last night he's also she has Asperger's um and you know she I mean he did come up crying
last night because the chat was making fun of him and stuff and I felt kind of bad but I do feel
a little bit of that, because then it will make him stronger.
But yeah, much for him, I'll have to make that judgment.
But I'm happy to have him on the show for right now.
But I do believe he's autistic.
I do believe an autistic is like, you know,
he focuses on a few things and he.
Oh my gosh.
That's interesting clip.
This is the Mason saga.
It is a saga, isn't it guys?
Who knows what will happen next?
I mean, it's just crazy.
Um, let me see. How about to use it for yourselves with this one multiple times? Hey, what's up Canada dry Canada dry?
I do want to say thank you Canada dry
I'm not gonna like get mad at you for going to that job
I'm not gonna get mad at anybody for going to that show. It's on what they say
And you didn't say anything bad about me. You just mentioned Christine and there were like
Yeah, that was that was a whole thing. I guess Christine was crashing across now again
Well, not really crashing out, but she did not like Canada dry
Yeah, they don't get along too well, but I'm not gonna get mad again in a drive in Canada drive
And I have had our differences of course in the yeah, you just mentioned Christine
We've had our differences in the past. I hope we were cool now, and it's like yeah
I know Christine really doesn't get along with really too many people like really she's
She's got quite a few enemies like
Like nobody like goes after her and she just makes up these lies and just like goes after these random people like
Like she made up that lie about me and flirty diamond. I'm like, what the hell like lady
You don't even know me like I don't even get down like that
It's okay if you date it flirty. I'm not gonna judge you brother. No, trust me. If I got down that way
I'd be open about it. I'd be open about it
Well, I don't know about that
Hello, oh shit. That was you me. Sorry. You mean
That's okay. I think
It's all happened not because of between you and you know miss beta, but
Some people around
between of you two
Why controlling there like I said try manipulating
Try mix
If it's like if you're trying to like get do some stuff socially or something through like other like
Interpreting relationships. What is that except?
You know manipulation like and that is what it's happened. So
We'd like to see another song you meet. Did you see this one? It has a Japanese sound to it. Do you want to hear this one?
It's good for Halloween
Japanese
Konnichiwa
Konnichiwa. Oh, hey, oh, hi, maaas. Ah
Suzuki
This is all in Japanese
Oh, we have someone coming up on the panel. Who's this? Oh, Alexander McQueen. Uh-oh. What do you think about this, Yumi?
I got a song for you Yumi.
Japan Bumper Harbor.
I don't know about war. Stop it. I don't know what he's talking about. Sorry Yumi.
Um, jeez, Louise, bring up something from a million years ago, Alex.
Okay, you want to hear a song?
Let me see.
Um, the number is probably like number 20.
I just played.
You just played for me.
Oh.
Let's hear me sing.
So you want my fire
No I don't crave it
But I light it
Stepping through my storm
No I won't fight it
I'll ignite it
Keep it strange divine, no morning after, no rewind
This feels like a glitch in fate, we don't heal, we just create
Be the kind of soul you can only touch in the astral
Yeah, we don't ride waves, we become the tidal
Devotion, maybe we should drop Emotion, that can be your vice, yo
Come too far gone in nights like this
You don't need to call in sick
You're already inside the mystic
Call it devotion
Maybe we should drop emotion
I can be your vice
You're omen
You're not the only one who's chosen
Where'd you even go?
You just left me alone?
I was thinking, what was I going to maybe share with you?
I don't know, forgot.
Well, is that it? Everyone's mad at me.
You did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you did you
Cash app or whatever on it and they start their show it's a good way to start
It's like but I'm like I need to have my own website
And so I've been designing and working really hard on it. It looks really really good
It's actually stuff is working falling into place. I'm gonna be able to
Put the panel verse with that
Also, I did an astrology report today for somebody. I'm so excited
And I think that person for asking and I think that they're going to love the report. I hope they love it.
And, uh, oh yeah, I was going to say maybe if I can find this is like something I did last night like the last thing I did.
Hmm, that was yeah, here we go
Well, let's hear it, okay
World premiere
my heart, cheers.
ghost in my own machine the demons they got VIP passes shifting faces eating
static whispering your eyes and traffic they crawl through my circuits chanting
reverse like angels the flunk their universe
Curse the reason
Yo, yo, yo, one of the worst you've ever had. Well, I
Don't know sometimes even the worst turn out to be the best sometimes. That's what they call a cult classic
What's up, Alex?
That was a good song man, thank you
Yeah, some of these are really like
Based on like other songs that really mean a lot to me and it's like just a way to like kind of like
What is that? Oh sine mean psyche awakens to be the like
That means five pH. It's the it's a it's a kind of like
Yeah, I know the number right by the perfection or something right some yeah, but it's also like yeah, yeah
It's a PHI PH like five
like Phi Beta Kappa, it's like psychiatry, you know, PSY sometimes, you know.
It represents.
Yeah, it means, you know, psychiatry.
But yeah, it's a great character.
It's a Greek letter meaning five my right thing that is remember I think I'm what that was a mean though
What is the represent?
Looks like the leapers
It looks like a fucking cup like a I don't know pitchforks like what the hell is that looks kind of like it's I know what the moon means
This is mr. You mean nobody has your opinion. Hey, so what is your question I'm back
What the fuck said don't sign in the middle of the thing by
Everything that is is great. I know I heard that. Well, what the fuck does that mean? It means like psychiatry
It's like the means the mind. What do you mean psychiatry? Hold on
The same so I gotta look in the dictionary now what psychiatry means and that's what that signal
We agree. I'll agree
Psychiatry, yeah, it's from the word psyche and so is psychic. What the fuck is psychiatry?
It's a study of the mind
Study of the mind. Oh my god
My mind influences behavior and so so forth and
It can be very complicated, but we have basically a Freud study of the
That's what that means
Yeah, that's bad and say you know me
Starting in mind
With a moon a star and then the all-seeing eye on the back of the dollar bill
So say hi
Thank you. No, I was fucking, you know
Shut up. Oh mr. You me
It's a, it's a, I love a, or it's a crescent moon is, which is like, that's hilarious.
I knew, I knew it was a comedian.
You never been, you never been an ancient woman.
That's why you call me as a man.
The story of the mind.
He said,
Let me look at it
Who's starting the mind though who who's the doctor studying the mind you are you are you doctor side?
He holds on you me. I'm trying to get to the bottom of something
Who the fuck is starting the mind because he has an insignia you dumb Filipino bitch get out of here
He has an insignia
That represents psychiatry, which supposedly means the study of the mind
So who is studying the mind and whose mind is getting studied?
Are you starting beaters mind?
I'm starting to beat his mind, what a dick!
Alex I'm not okay. Listen. It says a side letter most commonly first the Greek letter side, which is a symbol for the field of
psychology is a
Listen bro
Can you put that thing down so I can see myself on the screen enough it is hiding Alex
Put the fucking dome and say you're done. I mean psychiatry. All right, pal and put my hands on my head back up there
What's going on here
You me
Oh, God, okay, you'll set up, set up for a minute, okay.
Mr. Yumi.
How are you doing, Mr. Yumi?
I'm kicking you off.
Well, he muted, okay.
I'm laughing at you Mr. Alex, I should explain, so it's the opposite letter.
You really need to go to the hospital Mr. Alex.
It's okay, it's fine.
I'm sure you've never been with any Asian woman.
That's why you never met.
I love Indian women.
I give up, you guys.
You mean you have inverted nipples?
Do your nipples go in or do they pop out?
You nipple
Why on your tits do they pop out and if they do
When you get horny, do they grow and become like string beans?
Why are you so disgusting me?
You're really disgusting.
No, no, I'm studying biology.
I'm taking a course in university.
And I'm studying biology.
So I'm taking surveys from women all over the world.
You mean you have to help me.
You have a dick.
I have a vagina.
So wherever, wherever you are from, do your nipples, if you're, if you're, if you're big, it's still so lonely, go, go to the outside, find a woman, and then go fuck her.
Was the Alex are you under the water or something would happen?
It's wrong. Yes, Mr. Alex. It feels so lonely.
Go to the outside. Go to the outside now.
Find a woman. Find a woman. Go fuck her.
You're not telling me on here.
I'm here to support Mrs. Ivy, okay?
So you want cock in your ass
That's what she's saying in cold. I don't want to hear about cock in her ass. Okay. I don't
Hey, dude, what are you talking about? Don't lie. You want to hear more? Oh my god. Where am I now?
Did I go to an alternate universe?
You meet doesn't want to hear about cocking our ass. Okay, maybe
You don't want to hear about cocking your ass. Come on
Am I in the toilet zone here? Where the fuck are the candid camera, bro?
Go outside, go outside, go outside.
Both of you went top in your ass, and that's a fact.
Mr. Union.
Go outside.
Go to the outside.
Hey, listen, Mr. You need to go to the outside go to the outside find a woman and fuck her
No, I don't find a woman why you can bring me on my energy time and come okay, and
And put me in the green
I'm an old woman
I had enough women baby. The next woman I have. Don't worry about it. Why don't you go outside
and find God because you know you want God. Remember God? God owns you. God owns you some
Don't fuck up. Okay. Okay. Shut the fuck up
Okay computer, I'm using my phone idiot
Idiot, how do you spell idiot?
Belly is for me
Really, right? It's capital E
Right capital E. How do you spell idiot?
You idiot, okay? Idiot
It sounds like a fucking
China disease
You have an Indonesian disease and you're pussy
Fucking
I'm from Indonesia. I'm Yumi.
You're so lonely.
I'm Yumi.
Your thing is so lonely.
You have my only dick.
I'm Yumi.
That's really sad.
Mr. Alex.
You're troll.
Maybe you're the biggest role that I ever met
No, my talk is the biggest show you ever met, bitch
Yeah, remember my talk relax. I'm the second biggest show. My dick is the first phase until someone exposed your real looks
Sorry, mr. You mean does that hurt you?
No, it's not
Asian woman like me. That's why you're calling me as a mister. I don't care
Yeah, a troll like you a troll like you will act like that will attack me like that
Will will troll like me like that has a man has a trunks has a big has a catfish. I don't care
I have all my proofs. I have value. I have education. I have my job. I do my things.
I have my real life. Unlike you Mr. Alex, what do you have? A zero?
Huh?
Are you drowning, sir Alex? Drowning in the deep, deep blue sea.
I wish you, you do.
Ah, thrall, thralls, cyber thralls.
Wait, Bronzeberg's still here?
Oh, Bronzeberg's still stalking?
Show yourself in public. Would you I don't get it having having the one case of scribes
without any
filling this face in a public but
this person
Attacks someone
With uh, you know
Are you drowning you stand you? Can't even understand you?
You don't know Blancford
No one can understand you stupid bitch shut up
You dumb brat
Go get up your blue crayon
Are you part of a flying monkey in your blue crayon and paint your face mr. You me
I feel sleepy because of you, Mr. Attic.
You're so boring.
You're boring yourself.
Yeah, I'm happy. Mr. Yumi. Do you use industrial paint? Is that like over one? Hold on. Do you use a crayon, a marker, or is that spray paint when you, when you come up like an animal with the blue face?
Oh, man.
How do you, what is that? What is that? Where do you buy that?
Why is your-
Indonesia blue face loser bitches are us?
What is that?
Where do you get that blue mask on?
Ha, do you actually go to a store and buy that paint?
Like, hey, I'm Yumi.
I'm Mr. Yumi.
Can I get some blue paint for my face?
You go home in your little bullshit fucking garbage
that you live in, like a garbage loser.
Cause I feed you dumb room.
Shut up bitch. Shut the fuck up. You don't have a pot to piss in. You don't got a pot to piss in.
And then you put the little blue paint all over your face.
You put the paint all over your face.
So you waste the only money you make all year long.
Because you make a dollar all year in Indonesian money.
And you spend it on blue paint.
to call your faith. So your Indonesian ass makes $3 a year and you spend it on blue paint.
So God can make fun of you. Blue paint based that makes $3 a year. You make $3 a year and
You ugly bitch!
No, I can't read. I don't know what that is. I don't look at loser shit.
You make $3 a year and you spend it on blue paint.
Oh, are you gonna show us your paint kit?
Is that your paint kit?
Oh, God!
Is that what you...
Did you just show us your 300 year paint kit?
Oh, my God!
Yeah!
Paint it for us, you clown!
You clown, baby!
Can we see you painted?
I'm gonna mail you a dollar so you can buy red lipstick and make the whole clown face put it together, okay?
So you miss it is the red lipstick and the red nose bitch
Hey, Alex roll. Are you transgender? Are you stressed? Are you in serious depression? Oh
Yeah
are you are you are you and now if you pay attention to center ring you mean okay the
fucking human clown bitch Indonesia he comes you me with a little face and a
little red nose I'm gonna buy you the red nose and the red lips you got the
blue face bitch you so I'm gonna hide my circuit you're gonna be my number one
You're gonna come out and jump in.
The Yumi, the clown.
I'm Yumi, I'm Yumi, I'm Yumi.
Guess who's gonna be ringmaster, bitch?
Gotti.
Gotti's gonna be in a top hat with a whip.
Whip in your stupid ass.
He's the little bitch clown
Yeah
And you're gonna do two acts not just that after intermission you're going on again, bitch
You're going on again. So in the back
God he's gonna whip your ass you little clown bitch
and I'm paying for the nose and the red lipstick I'm paying for the lipstick you clown are you coming
in your pants it's your dirty pussy coming
Ew, imagine you sitting down and pissing and shitting.
Ew, Indonesian pussy, that's disgusting.
Ew, yo, I'm gonna throw up right now.
Imagine this dumb bitch shitting, wiping her nasty poo.
Got lost, Alex 12.
Oh my god, Alex 12.
Why he act like that?
Why he keep saying that I'm a man?
don't have a pussy I don't have white vagina or something that's really sad I'm
sorry I'm I'm truly sorry
I walk the crossroads even now
Your name burns behind my eyes
Three full goddess, mother of disguise
Through obsidian rain I hear
Faith like a flame
How to steal
I whisper through
Grow the light within the shadows
Yeah, you're gonna talk to Mr. Alex
Mm-hmm. Okay
Why mr. Alex? Why mist? Why is everyone mr. You mean?
Why not it's a sign of respect
No, not here. Hey, yes, but no, yes. No, I'm just I can live
I mean, I don't want to talk. I don't want to talk. I don't want to have a conversation with a troll like mr. Alex
I don't know if, you know, we don't call everybody Mr. and Mrs. here, everybody, we need to call their name, just Alex, you don't have to call them Mr.
Mr. Alex, in Indonesia it's not your culture, it's not your culture, it's mine.
Exactly, so in Indonesia everybody...
No, no, I'm just I'm wondering so in Indonesia you call out you have to call everyone mister like mister
Yes, yes, what if you don't know their name like if it's a mailman
Why you keep complaining
You don't, I'm sure you don't have any education, how to respect, younger than you, right?
Mr. Mr. Mr. That's a mindful.
Mr. Alice, so what? So if you don't like it, I will call you as Alice Roy.
No, Alice Roy. I will call you as a try.
You cannot bring me down
You really need
You don't have to come mr. Alex
All right, mr. Yumi
Okay
You want to troll me as a man, I don't care
I have my own proof. I'm an old woman. I don't care. You won't call it you won't call me has a man has a
Tron has a gay has a lesbo
Oh stop it. You're flirty diamond. You have a cock. You know you're another you're another
Tron
You have a cock just admit it. You mean you have a dick
With balls
You're born a man.
Where's your proof?
My proof is your picture.
Your blue face.
Every time you come up, that's my proof.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
You have seen me without you.
That's my proof, baby.
You freak.
19 inches.
You got fucking 30 inches down there.
Do you know what? I made a lot of trolls on YouTube using StreamYard. Yeah, they are using cleavage, nothing
Cybertrol always
Always like a spread line. All I've seen is a wooden desk
about someone else, when they strolls, never go on camp, never show themselves, when they
don't have any contact, when they don't have any contact, when they don't have any contact.
You're crying, when, when, who are you talking to? Who the fuck are you talking to you dumb
bitch? Nobody's listening, who are you talking to yourself? Who the fuck are you talking to?
No, who's day? Who are you talking to? First of all, your little speech, you just want to open a
little rent. But who the fuck were you talking to Garrett in the chat? The fuck are you?
Wait, no, hold on, hold on.
Chipley, Chipley, are you, are you Yumi friendly?
Hold on, Chipley, Chipley, are you Yumi,
do you like Yumi or do you not like Yumi?
No, no.
You know what, let me answer that question.
I don't like Yumi, I love Yumi.
All right, good, good, so get the bitch, get her.
Go boy, get her.
You're the new troll.
Fuck you, Yumi.
Right, right, right? I smoke crack. I smoke crack, right?
But there's no bitch.
Go fuck yourself, Alec. Go to the...
She probably has a Polish car, bro. I'm not buying.
Go fuck her, Alec.
It's a miracle that Chip became a Peter back me up, Yumi. That means something. That's...
The stars have aligned. I mean, now you're a full American.
You got a twisted nigger. I came out the back. You gave me a. You gave me a back.
Oh, really? But I just asked you if you liked or didn't like her and you said I don't like her.
So what do you mean you're here to back her up? No, I said I don't like her. I love her. I said I don't like her.
Oh, I missed that part. You love the bitch. Yeah, come on out.
That's true. That's true. And you don't have to say the R, but whatever.
but you love the donation okay well you know it's like you whatever just shut the whole thing down
and you know we'll just laugh about it and continue but but i do like to chip me honestly
i do like sometimes to watch it the next day and laugh
But sometimes we can't cuz he has to like erase it
Do you see the benefits of being Canadian you guys are just missing out
Wow
He was sure boy being gang hit the fucking link for once in your life
You
I love you me
We're gonna have sex one day and make a baby so we can
And then take me for everything I have
Huh, then you can just take everything I have for everything I have
I
Might if I knew what was going on
So we got a guy with a t-shirt on we got a guy with orange cuba cares we got mr. You me and me
Please
Me and mr. You me at the same time I can't hear what Joe sing because they got to keep the volume so low Joe. What was that?
I was saying you're gay
But beyond that you were saying something else
Me people are after me
This boy's about to get skinned on the panel.
Yeah, thanks for calling me today, Mr. Joe.
Me?
I was wrong all about you.
Yeah, you, boy.
Yeah, you.
I'm about to get skinned on the panel?
You're damn right you are.
Okay.
Well, I guess it'll be some entertainment.
What are you going to say about it?
Because you ain't got nothing to say.
Boy.
What can I say?
We know everything about you thing. That is we know every move you make
You push you push it you push this bleeding you push this bleeding
Oh, that's the best that's the best bro. They're so horny when they're bleeding. Yeah, it's really bad
Yeah, you're actually horny
They wanna get fucked so hard
Am I a man?
Am I a man on a troll?
When I pushy is a bleeding
No, you're not a man, you're just Mr. Yumi
Mr. Yumi, exactly. The hottest Indonesian not man we've known
You're a troll. You're really a troll, Mr. Joe
She says it to me 10 minutes to go
You have seen me many times to Joe, but why you why you
You never know me really
Oh, it's being up here with you and Mr. Yumi's scary, but nothing stands me more than things that is his teal shirt.
Things that is with the teal shirt.
That's someone eating you, like terrorist activity.
Honestly, man, if I knew it instilled such fear, I would have been wearing it every day for much longer.
Oh, no, no, no. That teal shirt is scary, bro.
Yo, yeah, one day's are awesome.
I'll invite a, you know, a devil, a damn man, black cardee, I guess.
Where's Alan Master Computer? I'll 69 him.
Instead of having to dirty your face?
I will 69 Alan Master Computer.
Before looking at that shirt, I love the way my hair is talking like this.
I can't think, I don't know if I'm on a, I'm on a therapy.
Do you want me to change shirts? It's laundry day.
No I do not, I'm kidding.
I don't have much left.
I got to change shirts.
The people take it like for real, I'm just kidding.
Mr. Yumi, why don't you shut up?
Can you show us your vagina?
that I believe you're a man I mean a woman if you have a daughter will you
agree when when a troll like Alex call this I'm not sure the party is going on
just a man she only had one kid I'm gonna put you a little tight though a
little
No, you're not you're an animal. You're an animal. You're a bore. You're like a wild boar for now
You're just a horny pig. You don't care about nothing
Of course, you're not a clown you're a wild boar. Yeah wild boar, bro. Yeah
Blueface bore you're a blueface bore
That's it. Yeah, that's too far. That's a little too over the top.
Boy, it's Chip. What are you talking about? You're supposed to back me up, my man.
No, I thought I would never think I would hear those words from my name out. She's a blue-faced boy.
That was just one. It's cock. Bull cock.
But he's bored and like I don't think that is like good
You won't got up here
Every single crab from your mouth Alex
You love me
So you love me
so you're a man and you love me
you just admit that I love them
yeah exactly that's all I got
I love you Alex
oh my god you love Alex
oh what a guy
she wants, I told you
but I'm already buying a ring
homo sapiens
who wants to be the best man
oh Alex you homo sapiens
don't even buy a ring just save the cock ring
homo sapiens
You're all horny over spunky
I can move to I ran and I ran you can have ten wise so
You're gonna gather them
in america and then me me and i ran summer spunky christine every dumb bitch all of you
i'm married all of you you can't even have one wife barely i mean kind of Jesus you better be over
Okay, that's all
Way ahead
You think I didn't think of how to marry sponky and mr. I
Was just as lost as you
Don't flinch, I've got the scars to prove it through
A doorway cracked inside my skull, let the shadowings crawl
I'm marching out of the dream, slow, quiet
Not giving up